(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To everyone who sent refreshments, thank you very much!
最高の瞬間を
The best moment
うまく行かない日だって
Even on days when things don't go well
そこにいて笑って
Being there and smiling
心の教科書 見ずに閉じたら
If I close the textbook of my heart without looking
何だってやれそうだ
I feel like I can do anything
落書きの中に光ってた想いを
The feelings that were shining in the scribbles
君とこうして探せたらなんて
Searching for them with you like this
嘘みたいだな
Feels like a dream
もっと また描いて記して
Keep drawing and recording even more
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a while until the performance begins.
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To everyone who sent refreshments, thank you very much!
そらちゃん！
Sora-chan!
ヘイ！ ヘイ！
Hey! Hey!
2025.10.2 Thu
Thursday, October 2, 2025
8th Anniversary Party
Starry Bl∞min'
with DJ ANKIMO
TOKI NO SORA
2024 6th year
ARE YOU READY?
8th Starry Bl∞min' Anniversary Party
最高だ 暴れちゃって 世界線 上書きしちゃって
It's awesome! Let's go wild and overwrite the worldline!
きっと 絶好調の先へ 行こうにゃん
I'm sure we can go beyond our peak. Let's go, nyan!
十六分音符の風 聞こえてきて何だかそりゃ
The wind of sixteenth notes... hearing it, I'm like, what is that?
無意識出す返事 それくらい揺らぐ
An unconscious response... that's how much I'm swaying.
もう一回 まだ覚めないで この指にとまれ
One more time, don't wake up yet. Gather 'round me!
追加投資頂戴 まだまだ足りない
Give me more of your support! It's still not enough!
SOS脳内
SOS in my brain.
もう一回 もう待てない 今すぐ会ってたい
One more time! I can't wait anymore, I want to see you right now!
全速力で
At full speed!
最高だ 暴れちゃって 世界線 上書きしちゃって
It's awesome! Let's go wild and overwrite the worldline!
君の音が聞きたいんだ
I want to hear your sound!
熱気が満ち溢れちゃって フレーム飛び出しちゃって
The heat is overflowing, jumping out of the frame!
一秒足らずの心 奪おう
Let's steal your heart in less than a second!
共鳴 絶好調
Resonance at its peak!
この声辿ってよ
Follow this voice!
夢思考 デラックスを奪おう
Dream thoughts, let's take the deluxe!
目覚めたらこの感情 アナログ変換して
When I wake up, convert this emotion into analog,
喜怒哀楽最高 一秒止められない
All sorts of emotions at their best. I can't stop for a second!
この状態どうだい 邪な進化以来
How's this state? Ever since the wicked evolution,
欲まみれ 限界行きたいな
Full of greed, I want to reach the limit,
予定で脱走 仕留められない
Escaping as planned, you can't catch me!
この状態どうだい 教えて会ってたい
How's this state? Tell me, I want to see you,
全速力で
At full speed!
最高が膨らんじゃって 世界線リンクしちゃって
The best is swelling, linking the worldlines!
君の熱を感じるんだ
I can feel your heat!
焦燥が満ち溢れちゃって 際限を壊しちゃって
Impatience is overflowing, destroying the boundaries!
一度きりの手を伸ばしたよ
I reached out my hand for this once-in-a-lifetime chance!
最高が膨らんじゃって 共鳴上書きしちゃって
The best is swelling, overwriting the resonance!
君に愛を届けるんだ
I'll deliver my love to you!
鮮度が満ち溢れちゃって 全てが溢れちゃって
Freshness is overflowing, everything is overflowing!
一度きりの有り余りにしてよ
Make it more than enough for this one time!
共鳴 絶好調
Resonance at its peak!
この声辿ってよ
Follow this voice!
夢思考 デラックスを奪おう
Dream thoughts, let's take the deluxe!
待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting!
描きかけたキャンバスに 鮮やかな彩りを
Adding vivid colors to the canvas I've started painting.
一歩ずつ踏み出して ここから始まったストーリー
Stepping out one by one, the story that started from here.
夢で見た景色は
The scenery I saw in my dreams...
憧れを叶えて
...granted my longings.
待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting!
この広い空で
Under this vast sky.
あの日から君と 越えた境界線も
Even the boundaries I crossed with you since that day,
待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting!
夢の方目掛けて
Aiming towards the dream!
きっと声 届いて
I'm sure my voice will reach you!
世界は広がって まだ続くこの先を
The world expands, and I'll continue on to what lies ahead.
夢みたいな色で まだまだ追いかけ続けて
In dream-like colors, I'll keep chasing after it forever.
チャレンジは止まらない
The challenge never stops!
手と手を繋いで
Hand in hand,
待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting!
今もずっとここで
Still right here, always.
いつの日か君が 見つけてくれる日まで
Until the day you find me.
待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting!
時空さえも超えて 君の元へ
Even transcending space and time, to where you are!
彼方へ...
To the distance...
届いて！
Reach!
待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting
時が変わっても
even if time changes
同じ星が奏でた 向こうへと
To the other side where the same star played
飛び立った友
my friend who flew away
寂しくても 何度でも
Even if I'm lonely, as many times as it takes
歓声を 原動力に変えて
turning cheers into power
ここまで歩いてきた
I've walked this far
私なら
if it's me
私 待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting
この広い空の下で
Under this wide sky
あの日から 君が微笑んだ
From that day, when you smiled
時に色づいて
the time became colorful
今 待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
Now, I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting
目指した あの場所で
At that place we aimed for
一言 届いて
reach with a single word
見つめて 届いて
Watch me, reach me
叶えて
make it come true
みんな、この曲待ってたでしょ？
Everyone, you were waiting for this song, right?
しっかり掛け声、覚えてきたよね？
You've properly memorized the cheers, haven't you?
一緒に「Fu Fu!」って盛り上がっちゃうよ！
We're going to get hyped together with "Fu Fu!"
せーの！
Ready, set!
我らが空の始まりは (パンパヤ)
The beginning of our sky (Panpaya)
惚れた瞬間 アレレレレ (パンパヤ)
The moment I fell in love, oh my oh my (Panpaya)
ほー、これは困った
Ho, this is trouble
二度ともとに戻らない
it'll never return to how it was
ダイバクハツ！
Big Explosion!
そして星が生まれまして (パンパヤ)
And then a star was born (Panpaya)
宇宙の鼓動 イチバンボシ (パンパヤ)
The heartbeat of the universe, the number one star (Panpaya)
あー、勝てやしない これは
Ah, I can't win, this is
次元を揺るがすくらい
enough to shake dimensions
ハッゲー！
Hugger!
このままハート撃ち抜いて
Keep shooting through my heart
どこまでも高い空まで
to the highest sky anywhere
見せてあげちゃう
I'll show you
さぁさぁさぁ 始まったこのライブは
Now, now, now, this live that has begun
あなたが熱狂待ってるって超新星
is a supernova where you're waiting for enthusiasm
してるから (してるから！)
because you are (because you are!)
夢中になっちゃうわ あなたにしています
I'm becoming obsessed, I'm doing it to you
出会った
since we met
さぁさぁさぁ あの風を覚えて
Now, now, now, remember that wind
ほら目の前でずっと笑い合っていたい
look, I want to keep laughing together in front of you forever
見てるの？ (見てるよ！)
Are you watching? (We're watching!)
聞いてるの？ (聞いてるよ！)
Are you listening? (We're listening!)
このビッグバンに気づいて
Notice this Big Bang
チュチュル チュチュル アイは地球ぐらいに
Chu-chu-lu chu-chu-lu, love is as big as the Earth
膨らんでこんなになってるよ
and has expanded to become like this
チュチュル チュチュル 宇宙の最果てまで
Chu-chu-lu chu-chu-lu, to the ends of the universe
この時の中で
within this time
の、さ！
it is!
少し、あなたのハートにキス
A little kiss to your heart
今更 意味深な顔して
now, with a meaningful face
めちゃめちゃ大好き
I love you so, so much
ちょっとの反応をくれ 可愛よ
Give me a little reaction, it's okay
喜ばせたいのさ
I want to make you happy
こんなの届かなきゃなんて 嘆かわしい
It's lamentable if this doesn't reach
我らの星の活動は (パンパヤ)
Our star's activity is (Panpaya)
割と古くても もももも (パンパヤ)
Even if it's relatively old, mo-mo-mo-mo (Panpaya)
いやー、これはすごいな
Wow, this is amazing
つまりあなたと私の恒星
in other words, the star of you and me
このままハート連れ去って
Keep taking my heart away
彼方を目指したなら
and if we aim for the far distance
見せてあげちゃう
I'll show you
あぁあぁあぁ 始まったこのライブは
Ah, ah, ah, this live that has begun
あなたが熱狂今頃超新星
is a supernova where you're currently in enthusiasm
してたか？ (してたかー！)
were you doing it? (we were!)
してたかー！ 今日まで続いて
We were! It has continued until today
出会った
since we met
さぁさぁさぁ ちょっと分かってね
Now, now, now, understand a little
今この場所でもっと早く行こうぜ
right now in this place, let's go faster
あなたと (あなたと！)
With you (With you!)
私で (私で！)
And me (And me!)
ビッグバンしたいの
I want to big bang
チュチュル チュチュル アイは地球ぐらいに
Chu-chu-lu chu-chu-lu, love is as big as the Earth
膨らんでこんなになってるよ
and has expanded to become like this
チュチュル チュチュル 宇宙の最果てまで
Chu-chu-lu chu-chu-lu, to the ends of the universe
この時の中で
within this time
の、さ！
it is!
みんなー！
Everyone!
見えてるよー、聞こえてるよー！
I can see you, I can hear you!
今日も、二日目、ソラパ 2025ですよー！
Today is the second day of SoraPa 2025!
みんな、聞こえてるよ。みんなの声。
I can hear everyone. Your voices.
可愛い、ありがとう。
So cute, thank you.
オレンジジュース美味しいよ。
The orange juice is delicious.
えー、昨日もやりましたが、今日もね、あの、かけ声、
Well, we did it yesterday too, but today,
みんなでやっていきましょうね。
let's do the call and response together.
じゃあ、というわけで...
Alright, and so...
あー、お久しぶりなんですよ。ま、昨日ぶりだから、ま、1日ぶりですね。
Ah, it's been a while. Well, since yesterday, so it's been one day.
ま、今日も2日目だよって人！
Well, who here is attending the second day today too?
おっ、今日が初めてだよって人！
Oh, who here is here for the first time today?
そもそもライブ自体初めてですよって人！
And who is at their first live performance ever?
おおー！じゃあ、ライブデビューですね。ありがとうございます。
Ooh! Then it's your live debut. Thank you very much.
では全員に声出してもらいたいな。
Now, I want everyone to let out their voices.
とりあえず、全員ー！
First of all, everyone!
声出せるかな？出せなかったら、ま、手で振るだけでもいいよね。
Can you shout? If you can't, just waving your hands is fine too.
女の子ー！
Girls!
ありがとう。男の子ー！
Thank you. Boys!
2階席ー！
Second floor!
海外のみなさんー！
Everyone overseas!
コメントー！
Commenters!
今、イェイイェイって言ってくれてる、イェイイェイって言ってくれてる。
They're saying "Yay, yay" right now, they're saying "Yay, yay".
そして、えー、左のみなさんー！
And, everyone on the left!
右のみなさんー！
Everyone on the right!
全員ー！
Everyone!
最高じゃないですか。みんな、声枯らす準備できてるって感じ？
Isn't this the best? Do you feel ready to lose your voices?
見えてる、見えてる。前の方、後ろの方...
I see you, I see you. The people in the front, and in the back...
前の方、後ろの方、どこ見てんだろうね。
Front, back... I wonder where I'm looking.
はい、というわけで、あー、ありがとありがと。
Yes, and so... ah, thank you, thank you.
いやみんなのね、応援も、今日なんかクオリティ高いね。
Man, your support today... the quality is high.
めちゃくちゃ青い。なんか、世界が青い...
It's so blue. Like, the world is blue...
あ、クオリティじゃないのか。もしかして、あれかな？
Ah, maybe it's not "quality"? Is it because of that?
今回のライブのTシャツの人もいる？
Are there people wearing the T-shirt for this live?
あ、やっぱそうだよね。Tシャツも青だもんね。
Ah, as I thought. The T-shirt is blue too.
すごい、ありがとうございます。もうね、
Amazing, thank you. You know,
みんなが外で写真撮って、「来た！今から！待ちきれない！」ってやってるの、
I saw everyone taking photos outside, saying "I'm here! It's starting! I can't wait!".
すごい見てましたからね。ありがとうございます。
I was watching you. Thank you so much.
とね、こうやって喋ってるんですが、えーYouTubeをご覧の皆さん。
So, while we're talking like this... everyone watching on YouTube.
なんと、まだ来たばかりなんだけど、ま本当に3曲しかやってないから、
Although we just got started, and we've really only done three songs,
まだ来たばかりかもしれない。
so it might still be just the beginning.
いや、物足りないなーって思う人、ぜひね、なんかどっか、
If you feel like it's not enough, then please,
ここ、ここ、ここ、ここ、どっかに概要欄があるので...
there's a description box somewhere, here, here, here, here...
そこから、配信チケットとかで続きを見てもらえると、
if you could check out the rest with a streaming ticket from there,
私、噛んだ、とっても嬉しいなと思います。
I... I bit my tongue... I would be very happy.
というわけで、早速ね、お喋りばっかしてたらただの雑談枠になっちゃうのでね。
Anyway, if we just keep chatting it'll turn into a normal chatting stream.
次の曲に、行こうと思うんですが。
So, I think I'll move on to the next song.
まあね、昨日歌ってなくて待ってた曲、あるんじゃない？
Well, there's a song you've been waiting for that I didn't sing yesterday, right?
次の曲は、イェーイ！
The next song is... yay!
ニューアルバムから、ダンサブルな、
From the new album, a danceable,
ダンス・ダンス・ダンスの曲を歌ってみようと思います！
dance-dance-dance song is what I'm going to sing!
ご視聴頂きまして、ありがとうございました。
本日の公演は終了いたしました。
Thank you for watching.
Today's performance has ended.
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
★ライブチケット購入はコチラ>> SPWN
The free preview broadcast ends here.
★ Purchase live tickets here >> SPWN
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
★ライブチケット購入はコチラ >> SPWN
The free introductory broadcast ends here.
★Click here to purchase live tickets >> SPWN